CURRICULUM VITAE



Contact



0771 647 196 || 0737 157 573





66 Nelson Mandela Ave

Personal Profile

Name: Isaac Tenesi

ID number: 63 2071748 H 42 Passport number: EN257412

Driver's License number: 23331DJ(Cl Date of birth: 24 September 1992 Gender/ Marital status: Male/ Single

Nationality: Zimbabwean Religion: Christian

Professional Experience

Current Employer: Timeless photos
Position Held studio photographer, photo editor, office management
Pariod of amployment: Enbruary 2012 - Present

Period of employment: February 2013 - Present Scope of work and exposure

- indoor and outdoor photography
- Overseeing inventory and ordering of photography and video supplies.
- Supervision and monitoring of production processes
- Handles in line products and finished products.
- Compiling technical reports
- Evaluation of pictures and videos for weddings and corporates
- Conducting market preference surveys.
- Compiling quality control reports.
- Supervision and training of students on attachment
- Conducting performance evaluations on trainees and new staff.
 - Cleaning and maintaining he studio and the office

Profile

I am a hard working man whose ultimate goal is quality assurance. I am a mature, self motivated person who is resourceful and well able to work with others in high pressure environments. I have worked at Timeless Photography company for more than 10 years. My strengths include good communications skills, attention to details, and good judgement, the ability to initiate and coordinate team work as well as maintaining good working relations with colleagues

Key achievements

I was able to carry out daily office duties, operating cameras, studio setup filing both pictures and office paper work. I was able to improve the studio pictures, both quality and poses. I can also maintain and service the computers and printers that I use.

English language proficiency

- Excellent spoken and written command of the English language.
- Medium of instruction during studies and training programs was English.

Academic Qualifications

Bachelor of Information Technology Honors (BITH) Zimbabwe Open University (ZOU), (DEGREE)

Ordinary level

Epworth High School; (2007-2010)

5 O level passes, including Mathematics, English and Integrated Science.

Professional Training

Training: Computer operation and Packages (October 2015) Training firm: CUTMAK TRAINING SERVICES

Computer literacy.

- Internet
- *Microsoft office* (Ms word; Ms Excel; Power Point; Ms Access)
- graphicsgraphics(CorelDraw and Adobe Photoshop)

Hobbies

- Reading
- socialising

References

Leah Nachipo: Timeless Photos Managing Director timelyfotos@gmail.com
0782727071

Mrs Mutizwa : Former Timeless Photos Manager 0773 415 974

Stephen Kalajila: Matrox (Pvt) Ltd photography 0772 688 329

Mr Shin: I love photo(photography company) 0778 052 117

Ega Mudavanhu: Art & Design.Photograpy and video filming 0772 662 114